"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
任何超过一万美元的东西 都要登记
Anything over $10,000 has to be declared.
你... 没有... 登记这个
You... didn't... declare this.
先生 你得和我走一趟了
Sir, you're gonna have to come with me.
- 我跟你们的人说了 我什么也不知道!  - 老兄 冷静点!
- I told you people, I don't know anything!  - Dude, just calm down!
- 你干嘛跟踪我?!  - 是你妻子让我来的! 有件事非你莫属
- Why did you follow me?!  - Your wife sent me! Something you have to do.
她说 你得阻止那个黑衣人
She said you have to stop the man in black.
你得阻止他离开这座岛
You have to stop him from leaving the island.
九头蛇岛上有什么?
What's on Hydra Island?
飞机 把你朋友带回来的那架飞机
A plane. The same plane that brought your friends back.
所以我想让你去那边 探探虚实
So I want you to go over there and do some recon.
你是谁?
Who are you?
放下武器!
Put your weapon down!
带我去见你们的头儿
Take me to your leader.
那你跟我说说 是谁派你到岛上来的?
So why don't you tell me what brought you over to this island?
John Locke派我来的 我们做个交易吧 老大
John Locke sent me. Well, here's the deal, chief.
我回去告诉他 海岸边什么都没有
I'll go back over there and tell him the coast is clear,
我连人影都没发现
that I didn't find anybody.
然后我把那个老头带到你门口
Then I'll bring the old man right to your doorstep.
交换条件是什么 James?
And what do you want in exchange, James?
你让我们安全地离开小岛
You give us safe passage off the island.
想来些可可吗?
Want some cocoa?
你哪儿来的可可?
Where'd you find cocoa?
没有 假设而已
I didn't. Pretend.
腿怎样了?
How's the leg?
还是很疼
Still hurts.
你不必时时扎着绷带
You should leave the bandage off for a while.
- 多接触空气 对康复有好处  - 我会试试的
- The air'll do it some good.  - I'll try that.
介意我坐下来吗?
You mind if I sit down?
我知道 我们从没坐下来谈过话
I know you and I haven't had time to talk,
但我想知道 James是否把我在峭壁那儿
but I was wondering if James had filled you in
给他看的东西 告诉了你
on what I showed him at the cliffs.
你指的是 墙上刻满名字的那个洞穴
You mean the cave. The one with the names on the wall.
很多名字 现在都被划掉了
Most of the names have been crossed off now.
留下来的 屈指可数
There are just a few left.
"Kwon"就是其中之一
"Kwon" is one of them.
这名字是指我 还是Sun?
Does that mean me or Sun?
呃 Jin 我也不确定
Well, Jin, I'm not sure.
但这表明
But what it does mean
我们能离开该岛的唯一方式
is that the only way we can leave the island
就是将所有名字没被划去的人
is if all the names that haven't been crossed off
聚集起来
go together.
但Sun不在这里
But Sun's not here.
你把腿养好就行
You just take care of that leg.
这事交给我来办
I'm workin' on it.
嗯 Kwon先生
All right, Mr. Kwon,
这是您的行李箱和手表
here's your suitcase and your watch.
请前往美国海关
Please proceed to the U.S. Customs office.
钱呢?
Money?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
根据联邦法律 我们有权扣押您这两万五千美元
Federal Law says we have to confiscate your $25,000.
扣... 扣押?
C... confiscate?
换言之 如果您想要回这笔钱
It means that if you want it back,
就得把相关文书材料补充完整
you're gonna have to fill out the necessary paperwork.
呃... 钱啊
Uh... money.
先生 您可以走那边出去
You can exit right over there, sir.
走吧
你没事吧?
饭店那场会 我误期了
那笔钱是用来干嘛的?
我不知道
我们出门前 你爸塞给我的
他让我把钱 跟表一起送过来
我也没多问
一切都按他交代的做
有什么我能为您服务的吗?
May I help you?
我叫Paik
Paik.
Paik的预订
A reservation for Paik.
嗯 找到了
Yes. I've got it right here.
在8楼 我们为二位准备了一间绝美海景房
We've got a beautiful ocean view room for you on the eighth floor.
2间房 要2间
Two room. Two.
我们不是夫妻
No marry.
哦
Oh.
我叫Kwon 全名Jin-soo Kwon
Kwon. Jin-soo Kwon.
抱歉 真是对不起
I'm sorry. I apologize.
嗯 Kwon预订了一间单人房
Yes, there is a separate room reservation for Kwon.
842号房 请拿好 先生
Room 842. Here you go, sir.
Paik小姐 Kwon先生 欢迎来到洛杉矶
Miss Paik, Mr. Kwon, welcome to Los Angeles.
我离开一会儿 有事要办
I'm leaving for a little while. I got an errand to run.
什么时候回来?
When will you be back?
明早
Morning.
我不在的时候 看好帐篷
Keep an eye on the camp while I'm gone.
我一无所觉
I don't feel anything.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
愤怒
Anger,
快乐...
happiness...
痛苦...
pain...
我没感觉了
I don't feel it anymore.
或许这样才是最好的 Sayid
Maybe that's best, Sayid.
这能让你随遇而安
It'll help you get through what's comin'.
你在干嘛 Hoss?
What are you doin', Hoss?
在那东西回来之前 我得离开这里
I'm getting out of here before that thing comes back.
什么东西?
What thing?
Locke啊
Locke.
你就待在这儿
And you're just sitting around here,
- 乖乖听他的话吧  - 我不听任何人的话
- listening to whatever he tells you.  - I ain't listenin' to nobody.
我告诉过你 我和Widmore有个交易
I already told you I have a deal with Widmore.
- 如果你冷静点儿...  - 你跟谁有交易 这无关紧要
- So if you just calm...  - It doesn't matter who you have a deal with.
我等得太久了 我得去找我妻子
I've waited long enough. I'm going to find my wife.
- 去哪儿找她?  - 我要回寺庙去看看
- Find her where?  - I'll go back to the temple.
如果她不在那里 我就去海边看看
And if she's not there, I'll try the beach.
我会找到Sun的 别拦着...
But I will find Sun, so stop trying to...
- 快跑!  - 啊!
- Go!  - Uhh!
- 啊!  - 啊!
- Aah!  - Uhh!
是这家伙吗?
Is this the guy?
没错 把他带走吧
Yeah. Let's take him.
迷失 第6季第10集
出牌吧 机长
Play your card, Captain.
现在干嘛?
Now what?
等着呗
We wait.
等... 什么?
Wait... for what?
等Richard回来
For Richard to come back.
别说我疑神疑鬼 但Richard在窜入丛林前
You'll forgive my skepticism, but the last thing Richard said
说的最后一句话
before he went stomping off into the jungle,
是我们身处地狱
was that we were all in hell,
而且他对我们接下来该干嘛 一无所知
And he had no idea what we were supposed to do next.
我敢打赌 他再也不会出现在我们面前
In fact, I would bet money we never see him again.
Hugo会找到他的
Hugo will find him.
他会追上他 然后把他带回来
He will track him down and bring him back.
除非Alpert被培根油裹住了
Unless Alpert's covered in bacon grease,
- 否则 我可不信Hurley能追踪出什么结果来  - 嘿 别说培根了
- I'm not sure Hurley can track anything.  - Hey. Don't talk about bacon.
Jacob没骗过我
Jacob has never lied to me before.
如果他说Richard知道该干什么
If he said Richard knows what to do,
那么Richard肯定知道该干什么
then Richard knows what to do.
他会回来的
He'll come back.
在那之前 我们等着就好
And until then, we wait.
西红柿种得怎样了?
How are the tomatoes?
枯死了
Dead.
我还记得你第一次在这儿种东西
I remember when you first planted this here.
仿佛是一百年前的事了
It feels like a hundred years ago.
你不相信Alpert会回来 对吗?
You don't believe Alpert's coming back, do you?
我不在乎他回不回来
I don't care if he comes back.
那我们...
What about us...
是接班人的事呢?
being candidates?
那又怎么样?
What about it?
Hurley带我去过一个灯塔
Hurley took me to a lighthouse.
是Jacob的灯塔
To Jacob's lighthouse.
那里... 有一面镜子 围绕着镜子
And... there was a mirror, and all around it,
刻着... 成百上千个名字
there were... there were hundreds of names written down.
我不在乎 我不在乎Alpert或接班人之类的事
I don't care. I don't care about Alpert or being a candidate.
Sun啊...
Sun...
我们来这里 是有缘故的...
There's a reason why we were brought...
我不想听这些人生目标 或命运之类的话!
I don't wanna hear about how this is our purpose or destiny!
拜托你走远点儿 让我一个人安静会儿
I just want you to go away and leave me alone.
是Jin啊...
怎么啦?
你爸让我绕了半个地球 去送表...
所以我得去趟饭店
要不要进来再谈?
我不想站在门口说话
现在都11点半了
饭店早打烊了
我还是得试试...
Jin啊...
这人是我爸的手下
没什么大不了的
你会在乎什么呢?
你不过是来这里购物的
你就是这么看我的?
觉得我就是来购物的?
不是...
或许你该告诉我 把扣子扣紧...
就像你在飞机上做的那样 如何?
那飞机到处都是人...
我不知道有谁在看我们
没人会看我们的
言归正传... 你想要我把扣子扣起来吗?
不想
那么...
这颗呢?
别扣
别扣...
这颗千万别扣...
Sun啊
Sun.
抱歉 我不想吓到你的
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to startle you.
心情不好吗?
Bad day?
你到这来干嘛?
What are you doing here?
我找到你丈夫了
I found your husband.
什么?
What?
我答应过你 要让你们夫妻团聚的
I promised you I would reunite you two.
只不过比预想中 多花了点儿时间
Took me a little longer than I thought it would.
他和我的人 在小岛另一头的营地
But he's with my people back at my camp across the island.
我现在就可以带你去找他
I can take you to him right now.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
你把寺庙里的人都杀了
You killed those people at the temple.
那些人是非不分
Those people were confused.
他们受骗了
They were lied to.
我也不想伤害他们
I didn't want to hurt them.
他们本来可以选择跟我一起走的
Any one of them could've chosen to come with me.
现在 Sun 我把这个机会留给你
And I'm giving you that choice, Sun, right now.
我不会强迫你做任何事
I would never make you do anything against your will.
我是在请求你
I'm asking you.
拜托
Please.
跟我走吧
Come with me.
Jin在等你呢
Jin is waiting.
Sun啊!
Sun!
Sun 等等!
Sun, wait!
我有个主意...
什么主意?
我们逃跑吧
什么?
我说真的
我们逃跑吧
怎么跑啊?
我存了笔钱
你早就计划好了?
生气了?
没有...
但你说的... 不能这么做
你想不想和我在一起?
当然想 我爱你
那好
有件事你得知道...
会是谁?
不知道
我挂标牌了啊...
就说你在睡觉
嗨 Paik小姐
Ms. Paik. Hi.
我是Martin Keamy
I'm, uh, Martin Keamy.
是你父亲的朋友
I'm a friend of your father's.
我想你有东西给我 对吗?
I believe you've got something for me. Hmm?
Sun啊?
Sun?
Sun 听得见吗?
Sun, can you hear me?
怎么了?
What happened?
还好吧?
You all right?
他在哪儿?
你说什么?
I'm sorry, what?
他刚才追着我...
他在这儿... 我看到了 他...
Sun 慢慢说 用英语告诉我怎么了
Sun, slow dowm. Tell me what happened in English.
是谁干的?
Who did this to you?
是Locke
Locke.
Sayid啊
Sayid.
嘿
Hey.
怎么了?
What happened?
我们被袭击了
We were attacked.
被谁?
By whom?
不知道
I don't know.
Jin人呢?
Where is Jin?
嘿!
Hey!
很奇怪吧?
Wow, that was weird, huh?
我在哪儿?
Where am I?
23室
It's called Room 23.
达摩组织当初在这儿
The Dharma Initiative
做关于潜意识信息的实验
was doing experiments on subliminal messaging in here.
你很了解达摩组织
But you know all about the Dharma Initiative,
是吗 Kwon先生?
don't you, Mr. Kwon?
- 为什么带我来这儿?  - 放心 你很安全
- Why did you bring me here?  - Relax. You're safe.
我要离开
I'm leaving.
对不起了
Sorry.
我们费了很大劲儿
But we went to a lot of trouble
才把你从那个岛带过来
getting you here off of the other island.
我不能让你离开
And I can't let you leave.
你们要我干什么?
What do you want from me?
这些地图... 是达摩成员用来
These are grid maps that... that the Dharma people used
标识电磁区的
to identify pockets of electromagnetism.
标这些的人 才能真的帮我离开这儿
Whoever signed these could really help me out.
呃 我知道... 我知道这些字迹很潦草
Uh, I know... I know the writing's difficult to read,
但... 但看着能确定是 "Jin-soo Kwon"
but... but it sure looks like it says, "Jin-soo Kwon."
所以...
So...
是你 对吗?
Is it you or isn't it?
你想知道答案?
You want answers to your questions?
那叫你们老大过来
Then get me your boss.
我要和Charles Widmore谈
I want to talk with Charles Widmore.
那么 你很走运...
Well, then you're in luck...
Kwon先生 他也想和你谈
Mr. Kwon, because he'd like to talk to you, too.
你水性好吗?
You a good swimmer?
- 挺好  - 用塑料包好
- Good enough.  - Wrap this in plastic.
别沾水 我们还得划船
You don't want it to get wet. We're taking the outrigger.
Claire 怎么了?
Something wrong, Claire?
嗯...
Um...
关于墙上的名字...
What... what you said to Jin...
你跟Jin说的那些事...
about the names on the wall...
你告诉他 需要聚集所有人 才能离开岛
You told him you needed them all to get off the island.
是的
Yes, I did.
那... 墙上有我的名字吗?
Was, uh... was my name on the wall?
没有
No.
那么我上不上飞机 都无关紧要了
Well, then it doesn't matter if I get on that plane, then.
- 我是说 你不需要我了  - 不 Claire 我需要你
- I mean, you don't need me.  - Oh, that's not true, Claire. I need you.
飞机上的位置 足够把我们所有人运走
And there's plenty of room on that plane for all of us.
那么 回到家后 Aron不认识我
Well, when we go home, Aron's not gonna know me.
和儿子形同陌路 他以为Kate才是他妈妈
Stranger to my own son. He thinks Kate's his mother.
墙上有她的名字吗?
Is her name on the wall?
没有 Claire 以后
No, Claire, it isn't,
都没有
not anymore.
但我需要Kate
But I need Kate.
为什么?
Why?
因为我... 有三个人不愿意离开这座岛
Because I'm... three people shy of getting off this island,
Kate能帮我让他们上飞机
and Kate can help me get these people on that plane.
一旦她完成使命...
But once she does...
那么该发生的事 就会发生
then whatever happens, happens.
这些枪要用来干什么?
What's up with the guns?
你们去哪儿?
You two going somewhere?
我们坐船去对面的岛
We're taking a boat ride over to the other island.
你还犯得着坐船?
What do you need a boat for?
你不是能化成黑烟 飞过去吗?
Can't you just turn into smoke and fly your ass over the water?
你觉得我要是可以的话 还会待在这儿吗?
Do you think if I could do that, I would still be on this island?
是啊 那样太荒唐了
No, 'cause that'd be ridiculous.
那么 你们到底去干什么?
What the hell you going over there for, anyway?
我以为你想躲开Charlie Widmore
I thought you were trying to avoid Charlie Widmore.
James 他们带走了我们的人
They took one of our people, James.
我要去救他回来
So I'm going to get 'em back.
哦 给我的?
Oh, it's for me?
真漂亮
Uh, this is really nice.
你的保镖该给我些钱
Your bodyguard is supposed to give me some money.
Kwon先生在哪儿?
Where's Mr. Kwon?
不懂英语
No English.
嗯?
Hmm?
好 请坐
All right, uh, sit down.
我搜过他房间 他不在
I checked his room. He's not there.
看下浴室
Check the bathroom.
好了 出来吧
Come on. Let's go.
Kwon先生 为什么不出来和我们谈谈啊?
Mr. Kwon, why don't you come and join us?
听着 谢谢你们的表 懂吗?
Look, thank you for the watch, okay?
但还应该给我
But you're also supposed to give me
装钱的信封... 内有2万5千美元
envelope with money in it... $25,000.
懂吗?
Yeah?
怎么办?
我们匀出点儿钱 给他们吧
你想把我们的钱给他?
住口
Stop that.
感觉就像该死的"哥斯拉"电影场景
I feel like I'm in a damn "Godzilla" movie.
那家伙叫什么? 那个...
What's that guy's name? The, um, the Russian guy...
貌似会说九国语言的俄国佬
speaks, like, nine different languages.
Danny的朋友
Uh, uh, Danny's friend.
- Mikhail  - Mikhail 他会说韩语吗?
- Mikhail.  - Mikhail. Can he speak Korean?
- 我想会吧  - 好 把他找来
- I think so.  - Okay, go get him.
现在穿好衣服
Now put some clothes on.
那些钱被海关扣押了 但我有钱
她说 她爸爸给他们的钱 被海关扣押了
She says the money her father gave them was taken at customs.
这不关我的事
Mm, that's not my problem.
我们一起去银行 我把钱取给你们
她想让你允许他们去银行
She wants you to let them please go to the bank.
然后他们会把钱取给你
They will get it for you.
你带她去银行
You take her to the bank.
我把这位公子哥儿 带回饭店
I'll take Casanova here to the restaurant.
然后 我们在那里碰面
And then we'll meet there.
他会和Jin一起回饭店
拜托 请你千万不要把我和Sun的事情 告诉Paik先生
拜托了
他刚才说什么呢?
What's he whining about?
他希望你能够答应他 不把他俩苟且的事情
He wants you to promise that you won't tell her father
告诉她爸
that they are involved.
喔 你不用为这个担心
Oh, hey, don't worry about that.
懂吗? 我会为你守口如瓶的 好吧?
Okay? Your secret is safe with me. Okay?
只要你把钱取给我
Just bring me the money,
我们就可以开开心心地 过各自的生活了 好吧?
and then we can all live happily ever after, right?
什么?
What?
你误会我四次了 当时我正在采芒果
Oh, for the fourth time, I was gathering mangoes,
我发现她的时候 她已经昏过去了
and she was already unconscious when I found her.
- 你为什么就不相信我?  - 因为你越描越黑
- Why won't you believe me?  - Because you're speaking.
你头上肿起了个大包
You got a pretty decent-sized bump.
或许会有轻微的脑震荡
Might be a slight concussion.
你可以听懂我正在说什么
You can understand what I'm saying,
但是你现在仅仅只会说韩语了
but you can only speak Korean.
是这样的
她撞到了脑袋 导致她忘记了如何说英语?
She hits her head and forgets English?
这能叫人相信吗?
Are we supposed buy that?
去问问那个能和亡灵对话的人吧
Asked the man who communes with the dead.
这可能是失语症
It might be aphasia.
这是由精神创伤引起的
It's, um, a condition that's caused by trauma
继而影响到了你大脑的语言中枢
and affects the language center of your brain.
但是通常来讲 这种失语状态都是暂时的
But it's usually temporary.
Sun呀
Sun.
你会好起来的
You're gonna be okay.
你在笑什么呢?
What are you smiling about?
整理好行囊 我们要出发了
Pack your bags. We are leaving.
不许动!
Don't move!
把双手举起来!
Let me see your hands!
冷静 兄弟 我是为和平而来
Easy, friend. I come in peace.
你知道我是谁吗?
Do you know who I am?
你是Charles Widmore
Charles Widmore.
那你知道我是谁吗?
Do you know who I am?
很显然 你不是John Locke
Obviously, you're not John Locke.
我还知道你是个充满奇异色彩的人
Everything else I know is a combination of myth,
鬼怪一般 夜间在丛林里呼啸来去
ghost stories and jungle noises in the night.
通过这些...路标塔 我觉得你知我甚深
I think you know more than that, judging by these... pylons
你为什么要来这里?
Why did you come here?
你掳走了我的人... Jin Kwon
You took one of my people... Jin Kwon.
我不知道你在瞎扯些什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
有位智者曾经说过 这个岛上将会爆发战争
A wise man once said that war was coming to this island.
我想 战争已经到来了
I think it just got here.
我们到底要去哪里 Richard?
Where exactly are we going, Richard?
- Locke在哪里?  - 什么?
- Where's Locke?  - What?
- 你说 他曾经来拉拢你们 他有提过他在哪里吗?  - 九头蛇岛
- You said he came to recruit you. Where did he say he'd be?  - Hydra Island.
就是你飞机降落的地方
Which is exactly where you landed the plane.
- 你飞回了这里 对吗?  - 是的
- That you flew back here, right?  - That's right.
这个... 人想要离开这个岛
This... man wants to leave the island,
只有那架飞机可以做到
and that plane is the only way can do it.
你知道我们该去往哪里吗?
You wanna know where we're going?
- 我们得去阻止他  - 这是你的错吧?
- We're gonna stop him.  - This is your fault, isn't it?
- 算是吧  - 我们如何去阻止他登机?
- Sort of.  - How are you gonna stop him from getting on that plane?
我们只能把飞机毁了
We have to destroy it.
什么?
你要把飞机毁了?
那我们怎么离开这个岛呢?
为什么她不说英语了?
Why isn't she speaking English?
她在逃离Locke的时候 撞到了自己的脑袋
She was hit on the head when she was running away from Locke.
他又回来了?
He came back here?
什么... 他想要什么?
What... what did he want?
他和你说过什么? 你... 可以听懂我在说什么吗?
What did he say to you? You... you understand me?
当然能
我能听懂 你个蠢货...
但是你想要我们去帮你 毁掉我们离开这个岛的唯一希望...
你真是疯了!
我是来这儿找丈夫的...
然后我可以和他一起回家 我可没有想来拯救世界!
她说我很重要
如果那是真的 说明你需要我!
那么请你"记住"...
我哪里都不会去!
看来她不想去
I don't think she wants to come.
有什么问题吗?
Paik女士想知道 是否出了差错
Ms. Paik would like to know if there is a problem.
很抱歉 这里显示你的账户已经关闭了
I'm sorry. I'm showing that your account was closed.
存款余额为零
The balance is zero.
她说你的账户已经关闭了
这是不可能的
只有我知道这个账户
她想知道 是谁把账户关掉的呢?
If she may ask, who closed the account, please?
看来是... 她父亲做的
Looks like... her father.
Woo-Jung Paik先生曾经访问过这个账户
Mr. Woo-Jung Paik had access.
他把所有的钱 都转汇到他在我们首尔总行
The funds were transferred to one of his other accounts
的其它账户里去了
at our main branch in Seoul.
是你父亲关闭的账户
什么... 他为什么要那么做?
你觉得呢?
警告: 此门勿开
- 啊!  - 给我进来
- Uhh!  - Get in here.
进来 快点 进来
Let's get in. Come on. Get in.
怎么了?
What's going on?
我把他的头在门上碰了下
I bumped his head on the door.
拜托 Omar 你要小心一点呀
Oh, come on, Omar. You gotta be more careful than that.
这里交给我了
I got this.
你去把那个阿拉伯人抓进来
You go get the Arab guy.
注意点 我也是阿拉伯人
Hey. I'm an Arab.
赶紧去把他带过来
Just go pick him up.
对不起 把你的头碰到了
Sorry about that.
Omar很忠诚 但他总是粗手粗脚
Omar is loyal, but he lacks attention to detail.
你完全不明白
You don't really understand
我在跟你讲什么 对吧? 什么都听不懂?
a word I'm saying to you right now, do you? Nothing?
好吧 别动 明白吗?
All right. Just hold still, ok?
我准备把你绑在这儿
I'm gonna strap you here.
万一你听懂了自己身上即将发生的事
Just in case you figure out what's about to happen to you,
我可不能让你发疯
I can't have you freaking out.
我想你还不知道
I don't think you realize
Paik先生在知道 你对他的宝贝女儿做过些什么后
how unhappy Mr. Paik was when he found out
有多生气
that you were doing his little girl.
你知道那2万5千美金
Well, you know that 25 grand
是他让你转交的 对吧?
that you were supposed to deliver?
那是我揍你的劳务费
That was my fee for popping you.
据我所知
From what I hear, you know,
所有为Paik工作的人 都知道一条潜规则...
anyone who works for Paik knows the cardinal rule...
别碰老板的女儿
hands off the boss's daughter.
但是你... 你无法抵抗她的魅力 对吧?
But you... you couldn't resist her, could you?
人总是无法抗拒欲望的
The heart wants what the heart wants.
谢谢你
Thank you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
某些情侣注定无法永结连理的
Some people just aren't meant to be together.
你到底在想什么?
What the hell were you thinking?
对不起 我知道 我们都很惶恐
I'm sorry. I know. I know we panicked.
这根本就不应该发生
This was not supposed to happen for days.
- 我们是有行程安排的  - 听我说 他要离开营地
- We had a timetable.  - See, he was leaving their camp.
那你就应该让他走
Well, you should have let him leave
然后把他带到丛林里
and take him in the jungle.
哦 也许你应该找个雇佣兵来指挥
Well, maybe you should put a mercenary in charge
而不是找一位地球物理学家
instead of a geophysicist.
过去的就算了
What's done is done.
我需要你把潜水艇里的包裹弄出来
I need you to get the package from the submarine
然后拿到医务室去
and take it to the infirmary.
你能帮我这个忙吗 拜托了 Zoe?
Can you do that for me, please, Zoe?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
Kwon先生
Mr. Kwon.
关于我们对你做的那些事
My deepest apologies for everything
我深表歉意 我叫...
that's been done to you. My name is...
我知道你是谁 你为什么把我带到这儿来?
I know who you are. Why did you bring me here?
我们搜过那架Ajira航空公司的飞机 发现了你妻子的行李箱
We searched the Ajira plane, discovered your wife's luggage
在里面找到了这个
and found this inside.
我想你可能会想要拿走
I thought you might want to have it.
继续
Go ahead.
打开它
Turn it on.
她的名字是Ji Yeon
Her name is Ji Yeon.
你的女儿
Your daughter.
我知道 你和她素未谋面
I understand you've never seen her before.
我也有个女儿
I have a daughter, too.
我知道骨肉相离是什么滋味
I know what it's like to be kept apart.
我明白 你想要的
I understand the one thing you want
是和你的妻儿团聚
is to be reunited with your wife and daughter.
但这些只能是幻影
But it would be short-lived
如果那个... 东西
if that... thing
打扮成John Locke的那个东西 一旦离开这座岛
masquerading as John Locke ever got off this island,
你的妻子 你的女儿 我的女儿...
your wife, your daughter, my daughter...
我们认识的 还有爱着的所有人...
everyone we know and love...
就会不复存在
would simply cease to be.
我来 是为了确保这事不会发生
I came here to make sure that doesn't happen.
怎么做?
How?
跟我来
Come with me.
我想 是时候让你看看包裹了
Think it's time for you to see the package.
那包裹是什么东西?
What package?
那不是样"东西"
It's not a "what."
是个"人"
It's a "who."
警告: 此门勿开
别杀我
求求你 放我走吧!
你是谁?
Who are you?
不懂英语
No English.
我不知道你为什么会在这儿 我也不在乎
I don't know why you're here, and I don't really care.
别走!
No!
放了我
Free.
放了我!
Free!
放了我
Free.
祝你好运
Good luck.
Martin啊
Martin
喂 Martin?
Martin?
这是谁干的?
Who did this to you?
看后面 你这个白痴
Look behind you, you idiot.
把枪放下!
别冲动
没事的
这些是谁干的?
我说把枪放下
快!
Sun 站远点
听见我说的话了吗?
扔掉枪 不然我就杀了你!
不 我想你不会...
因为 如果这些是你干的?
你早就开枪把我干掉了
Sun啊!
天啊! 天啊!
我带你去找人!
你不会有事的...
我怀孕了...
我给你带了点东西
I brought you a couple of things.
我想起了 曾负责过的一个病人
I was thinking about a patient that I had
当时我还在实习期
during my residency.
他遭遇车祸 头部撞伤
Car crash, banged his head.
醒来后 他就不能说话了
When he woke up, he couldn't talk.
那人当时很沮丧 我是说...
The guy was frustrated. I mean...
谁会不沮丧呢?
who wouldn't be?
然后一名护士说 "他不能说话...
And then one of the nurses said, "Just because he can't speak...
不代表他不能写字呀"
doesn't mean that he can't write."
你愿意试试吗?
Think you could give it a try?
愿意
交流起来 会比以前慢一点
It'll take a little longer to get your point across,
但至少你又能"说话"了
but at least you have your voice back.
我去过你的菜园 去看他还在不在
I went back out to your garden to see if he was there.
他不在 不过...
He wasn't, but...
后来我发现了这个
then I found this.
真是个顽强的西红柿
That's one stubborn tomato.
我猜没人告诉它 它本该枯死了的
Guess no one told it it was supposed to die.
对不起
别在意
Don't worry about it.
你不是第一个告诉我 让我别理你的人
You're not the first person to tell me to leave them alone.
Locke... 他跟你说什么了?
Locke... What did he say to you?
他说 Jin在他手上
你为什么不跟他走?
Why didn't you go with him?
我不信任他
你信任我吗?
Do you trust me?
Sun啊...
Sun...
跟我们走 我会帮你找到Jin的
Come with us, and I'll help you find Jin.
我会帮你找到他 然后让你俩都能登机
I'll help you find him, and I'll get you both on that plane
远离这座小岛 有多远 就走多远
and as far away from this island as you can get.
我保证
I promise.
你在想什么?
Where'd you go?
什么?
What?
你好像有点走神
Looked like your brain took a little stroll.
你为什么不担心 James?
Why aren't you worried, James?
我在担心
I am worried.
只不过 我成功地装出了不担心的样子
Just really good at pretending I ain't.
但我有种感觉 这一切快结束了
But I got a feeling this is almost over.
只要Locke带着Sayid划船到了对岸
'Cause if Locke rode over there on the boat with Sayid,
然后Charlie Widmore一拳把他打到水里 一切就结束了
then Charlie Widmore blew him right out of the water.
那如果他没有呢?
And what if he didn't?
哦 那我们就群策群力...
Well, then we're screwed six ways from sun...
哦 该死
Oh, hell.
就他一个人
He's alone.
我以为你过去找Jin了
Thought you went over there to find Jin.
他们说他不在那儿
They said they didn't have him.
- 你就信了  - 没有
- And you believed that.  - No.
Sayid在哪儿? 他也丢了?
Where's Sayid? Did you lose him, too?
James 你在那边的时候
When you over there, James,
你提到Widmore派人
You mentioned that Widmore had someone
把守着潜水艇里的一个房间...
guarding a room on his submarine...
里面是些他不想让你看到的东西
guarding something that he didn't want you to see.
对 然后?
Yeah, so?
我不喜欢秘密
I don't like secrets.
好了
All right.
- 好  - 这家伙几乎站不起来
- Okay.  - The guy can hardly stand.
噢 你还想怎么样?
Well, what do you expect?
哦!
Oh!
你给他用了多少?
How much did you give him?
显然 我给他用多了
Obviously, I gave him too much,
但这一路 我们就得让他昏着 我又不是护士
but we needed him knocked out for the trip. I'm not a nurse.
- 快来 把他架起来  - 我们走吧 Hume先生
- Come on. Get him up.  - Let's go, Mr. Hume.